# NATASHA DONGRE () Featured

Associate Consultant seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, System Analysis, Technical Architecture, Cloud Computing, Project Management, SAP HANA, SQL, SAP BO



Current Designation: Associate Consultant-IT Total Experience: 5 Year(s) 3 Month(s)

Current Company: Capgemini Notice Period: 3 Months

Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E.

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Mumbai, Pune [Electronics/Telecommunication]

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Associate Consultant, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, System Analysis, Technical Architecture, Project Management, SAP HANA, SQL, Tableau, C++, SAP BO, Business Objects

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 18-Jan-21 Last Modified: 18-Jan-21

### **Summary**

5 years of Information Technology experience in understanding and analyzing the technical and business requirements. Strong Understanding of Data Warehousing and Business Intelligence concepts

Expert knowledge of Database - SQL, Teradata, SAP HANA, BI Tools - SAP BO, IDT, CMC, SAP Applications Cloud, Lumira, Tableau.

Managed complete project cycle right from requirement analysis to system study, designing, coding, testing, de-bugging, documentation and implementation.

Hands on Project requirement gatherings, Design Docs, Requirement Review docs, Unit Test plans, UAT plan and User Trainings.

Possess good interpersonal skills that have been put to good use while coordinating with various Project teams.

Good interaction with Customers, Project team, Business users, Project stakeholders, multifunctional team environment.

Establish best practices, processes and focus on continuous improvement

Team player with effective communication skills.

## **Work Experience**

Capgemini as Associate Consultant-IT Jul 2018 to Till Date

Perform analysis, design, development, testing, and debugging of reports and dashboards.

Providing prompt solution to user issues and queries reported via Service Now Ticket

Efficient team player and helping my team members in solving their issues related to BOBJ

Good interaction with Customers, Project team, Business users, Project stakeholders, multifunctional team environment.

Enhancing and developing of complex BO reports from various sources.

Developing Visualization of data insights.

Birla Sun Life Insurance as Assistant Manager

Nov 2017 to Jun 2018

Roles and Responsibilities:

Ability in creating complex reports by using most of the business objects features using Web Intelligence

Worked with multiple data providers and freehand SQL to create reports

Created reports with different charts, Prompt filters as per Functional specifications

Accountable for providing high-end solutions to Business Objects customers and troubleshooting all issues related to development and administration.

Understanding customers Enhancements with-in the products and assisting them in proceeding further.

#### Ericsson as Assistant Engineer

Sep 2015 to Jun 2018

Project Overview: The objective of this project is to develop a platform to compare the various business metrics to take important business decisions. Also, to review team wise performance. Roles and Responsibilities:

Worked as SAP Business Objects analyst for ONEFM, ONETM, NIM Hands on experience of "Netcool" and "Remedy"

Hands-on experience of tools like ONEFM, ONETM, NIM for configuration and alarm management SPOC for data analyst to understand the business requirement and check with technical feasibility w.r.t BI Ability in creating complex reports by using most of the business objects features using Webi Intelligence Experienced in using Business objects functionality like functions, cross tab, formulas, and variables

## **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics/Telecommunication) from Lakshmibai Narain College of Technology, Bhopal in 2015

#### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
SAP BO3.x/4.x,SAP Information Design	4.2	2021	5 Year(s) 4 Month(s)
Central Management Console (CMC)			2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
SAP Lumira Designer 2.2	2.2	2020	1 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
SAP Analytics Cloud (SAC)			1 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
C++, SQL			5 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
MySQL, SAP HANA, Teradata			3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Windows XP/7/8.1/10			5 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

## Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
Hindi	Proficient			
Marathi	Beginner			

### **Affirmative Action**

Category: SC Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No

#### **Work Authorization**

Employment Status: Full time